HOLLY KEILY

SUMMARY OF SKILLS

Expert communication skills while maintaining professionalism in every situation. Variety of experience provides a thorough understanding of the processes, principals, duties, and cultural influences that any business, enterprise, or government organization must adapt to every day. Known for regularly showing initiative to take on responsibility for areas beyond basic duties. Able to respond to any population with a diplomatic mix of authority, discretion, and tact.

EDUCATION

Doctor of Philosophy, Linguistics in fieri

University at Buffalo, State University of New York, Buffalo, NY

Semantics, Psycholinguistics | Focus on language production and processing

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration 2010

Bachelor of Arts in French 2010

University of Denver, Denver, CO

Minor in Economics, Emphasis in Marketing

Cum Laude | Alpha Lambda Delta | Dean's List for Academic Achievement 2006-2010

Cherrington Global Scholar | Study Abroad in Avignon, France, 2008-2009

WORK EXPERIENCE

University at Buffalo Linguistics Department

Webmaster and Organizer for Tonal Aspects of Language 2016 Conference

2015 - Present

- Perform managing editor duties, including original content generation, content aggregation, copyediting, and proofreading the conference program
- Creation and maintenance of conference website, including submission management
- Event planning and management

Graduate Assistant in Accessibility Resources

2015 - Present

- Facilitate accessibility efforts for PhD student in Linguistics
- Prepare print material for machine reading, devise ways to convey visual data presentations non-visually
- Work one-on-one with student to ensure equal access to educational opportunities

Research Assistant to Dr. Jeffrey Good

2014 - Present

- Organize workshop for Cameroonian, American, and Italian grant participants
- Coordinate communication with grant participants
- Grant management, event planning and management
- Edit and prepare chapters of books and individual articles for publishing, including copyediting and fact checking
- Process reimbursement requests for co-researchers and Principal Investigators

Teaching Assistant, Lecturer

2012 - 2015

- Grade undergraduate activities, homework, and exams
- Prepare multiple chapters of two academic books for publishing, including copyediting and fact checking
- Plan and lecture for Linguistics 108, The Roots of English | Linguistics 207, Language, Society, and the Individual

2014 - 2015

Graduate Student Association, University at Buffalo

Member, Webmaster

- Update, reorganize, compose, and maintain website and social media accounts
- Write, edit, and post online content for website
- Source and preparation of images, tables, graphs, and charts
- Design graphics, create handouts and informational material for events
- Organize and present website design, development tutorials for graduate students

Graduate Linguistics Association, University at Buffalo

Member, President and Webmaster 2012-2013

2012 - Present

- Participate in all Linguistics Association events for personal and professional development
- Redesign and launch association website
- Organize and promote events, coordinated with the Graduate Student Association

United States Youth Soccer Association Referee

United States Soccer Federation Grade 8 Certified Referee

2000 - Present

- Officiate all levels of soccer including Premier 1, Champion's League, adult competition
- Act as lead and assistant referee for all levels of soccer
- Manage field players, sidelines, coaches, and spectators

Next Generation Wealth Management, Incorporated

Marketing Strategist

2011 - 2012

- Update, reorganize, compose, and maintain website and social media accounts
- Write, edit, and produce weekly emailed newsletters and printed quarterly reports for clients
- Organize and execute transition to paperless office
- Update, maintain, and merge customer relationship management system

Na Hoku, Incorporated

Customer Service Representative

2010 - 2011

- Lead customer service team
- Manage customer communications
- Interface, update, check, and maintain online stores
- Help develop new online sales technology
- Input, update, and manage Microsoft Great Plains items

Boa Technology, Incorporated

Sales and Marketing Intern

2009 - 2010

- Interface with Japan office to support and align communication
- Media analysis for domestic and international footwear market
- Event management
- Support domestic and international meetings with marketing and sales materials
- Leverage sponsored snowboarders to elevate the Boa brand via media relations, video development